UNITE Communications Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/037 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Communications Department Audio-Visual Materials
1990- 2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/037 AV
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
5757933
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 05, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/037: UNITE Communications Department Records 6000/037 P: UNITE Communications Department Photographs 6000/032: UNITE Communications Department Joann Mort Files
Textile workers--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Communications Department--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
5757933
- Autoliv - What time is it? Union time!, 1 (Box 1)
- December 21What time is it? Union Time!, 1994; 2 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Autoliv Campaign, Indianapolis, IN - 1994
- AutoLiv - 1994/December 21What time is it? (UNION TIME), 3 (Box 1)
- UNITE Get Ready to UNITE, 4 (Box 1)
- UNITE It's out turn to UNITE, 5 (Box 1)
- UNITE for a fairness at Dillards, 6 (Box 1)
- UNITE for fairness at Dillard's, 7 (Box 1)
- UNITE for fairness at Dillard's, 8 (Box 1)
- Mysterio en Megas UNITE, 9 (Box 1)
  Sapnish version
- Mysterio en Megas UNITE, 10 (Box 1)
- Mysterio en Megas UNITE, 11 (Box 1)
- Pillowtex It's time we had a say, 12 (Box 1)
- Pillowtex It's time we had a say, 13 (Box 1)
- Pillowtex It's time we had a say, 14 (Box 1)
- Estamos Uniendonos en Trend-Lines UNITE, 15 (Box 1)
  Spanish version
- Getting together at Trend-Lines UNITE, 16 (Box 1)
  English version
- UNITE It's our turn to UNITE, 17 (Box 1)
- UNITE It's our turn to UNITE, 18 (Box 1)
- UNITE Get ready to UNITE, 19 (Box 1)
- UNITE Get ready to UNITE, 20 (Box 1)
- Getting together at Trend-Lines UNITE, 21 (Box 1)
- Getting together at Trend-Lines UNITE, 22 (Box 1)
- Estamos Uniendonos en Trend-Lines UNITE, 23 (Box 1)
- UNITE - Dreisen #1 and #2, 24 (Box 1)
- UNITE! - Dreiser #3, 25 (Box 1)
- A Message from President Bruce Raynor, 2001; 26 (Box 1)
  November 2001
- Estamos Uniendonos en Trend-Lines UNITE, 27 (Box 1)
- It's union time at Dreison, 28 (Box 1)
  English -- Be Productions
- It's time for a real union! It's time for UNITE!, 29 (Box 1)
- It's time for a real union! It's time for UNITE!, 30 (Box 1)
- UNITE '99, 31 (Box 1)
- It's time for a real union! It's time for UNITE!, 32 (Box 1)
- Fieldcrest vs. the law, 33 (Box 1)
- Fieldcrest vs. the law, 34 (Box 1)
- UNITE '99, 35 (Box 1)
- Good for business, 36 (Box 1)
- UNITE! A message from President Bruce Raynor -- 12/06/2001, 37 (Box 1)
- Zeta - tape 3, 38 (Box 1)
- Un Mensaje de Chuck Hansen, 39 (Box 1)
- Fieldcrest vs. the law, 40 (Box 1)
- A union at Autoliv Can it really make a difference?, 41 (Box 1)
- Unions are good for business take a peek!, 42 (Box 1)
- Zeta -- Tape 2, 43 (Box 1)
- Zeta -- tape 2, 44 (Box 1)
- A message from Chuck Hansen - Pillowtex CEO -- 6/10/1999, 1 (Box 2)
- A message from Chuck Hansen - Pillowtex CEO -- 6/10/1999, 2 (Box 2)
- ARC Employees - Seeking Quality Treatment while giving quality care, 3 (Box 2)
- ARC Employees -- Seeking quality treatment while giving quality care, 4 (Box 2)
- A message from Chuck Hansen - Pillowtex CEO -- 6/10/1999, 5 (Box 2)
- A message from Chuck Hansen - June 17, 1999 - Plant 1, Ron Lisenby, 6 (Box 2)
- Pillowtex -- Video Two (Meeting Video), 7 (Box 2)
  Master
- Pillowtex -- Video 2, 8 (Box 2)
- Pillowtex -- Video 2, 9 (Box 2)
- Pillowtex - Video 3, 10 (Box 2)
- Pillowtex -- Video 2, 11 (Box 2)
- UNITE! Uniting at Levi's - San Benito, 12 (Box 2)
- El Paso - Levi Strauss UNITE, 13 (Box 2)
- El Paso - Levi Strauss UNITE, 14 (Box 2)
- El Paso - Levi Strauss UNITE, 15 (Box 2)
- Un Cambio Ahora en Manhattan Beer UNITE!, 16 (Box 2)
- Un Cambio Ahora en Manhattan Beer UNITE!, 17 (Box 2)
- UNITE! Uniting at Levi's - San Benito, 18 (Box 2)
- UNITE! All the way!, 19 (Box 2)
- UNITE! Power at work/Unite Local 340, 20 (Box 2)
- UNITE! All the way!, 21 (Box 2)
- Unite - Levi's Movin' up in Mountain City, 22 (Box 2)
- We're worth more: Union time at Akro, 23 (Box 2)
- We're worth more: Union time at Akro, 24 (Box 2)
- We're worth more: Union time at Akro, 25 (Box 2)
- UNITE! Florida Nursing Home Workers' Unite Campaign, 26 (Box 2)
- It's time for a REAL UNION! It's time for UNITE!, 27 (Box 2)
- It's time for a REAL UNION! It's time for UNITE!, 28 (Box 2)
- It's time for a REAL UNION! It's time for UNITE!, 29 (Box 2)
- Unite for a real union, 30 (Box 2)
- Unite for a real union, 31 (Box 2)
- Unite for a real union, 32 (Box 2)
- UNITE! Uniting at Levi's - San Benito, 33 (Box 2)
- Unite - Levi's Movin' up in Mountain City, 34 (Box 2)
- Unite - Levi's Movin' up in Mountain City, 35 (Box 2)
- UNITE! Power at work/Unite Local 340, 36 (Box 2)
- UNITE! Power at work/Unite Local 340, 37 (Box 2)
- Pillowtex Video Three (Meeting Video), 38 (Box 2)
- Pillowtex Video Three (Meeting Video), 39 (Box 2)
- A message from Chuck Hansen -- Plant 1 - Ron Lisenby -- 6/17/1999, 40 (Box 2)
- A message from Chuck Hansen -- Plant 1 - Ron Lisenby -- 6/17/1999, 41 (Box 2)
- Vote YES, 42 (Box 2)
- Vote Yes!, 43 (Box 2)
- American Cabinet Unites, 1 (Box 3)
- Flambeau Airmold Workers: Be encouraged, 2 (Box 3)
- Flambeau Airmold Workers: Be encouraged, 3 (Box 3)
- American Cabinet Unites, 4 (Box 3)
- American Cabinet Unites, 5 (Box 3)
- Flambeau Airmold Workers: Be encouraged, 6 (Box 3)
- UNITE! Tape - June 1995, 7 (Box 3)
- Greg Norman Collection -- Images Film Spring 1996, 8 (Box 3)
- Union protest at Sol Frank -- San Antonio, TX 5/13/1998, 9 (Box 3)
- UNITE! Tape - June 1995, 10 (Box 3)
- UNITE! Tape - June 1995, 11 (Box 3)
- Manhattan beer #4 -- Fla, Miami, Pittsburgh, 12 (Box 3)
  tape 2 of 2
- Manhattan beer #1 -- 2/7/1996, 13 (Box 3)
- Ennis Automotive No Mas Segundas Oportunidads!, 14 (Box 3)
- Manhattan beer #4 -- Fla, Miami, Pittsburgh, 15 (Box 3)
  tape 1 of 2
- Manhattan beer #2 -- 2/10/1997, 16 (Box 3)
- Manhattan beer #3 -- 2/11/1997, 17 (Box 3)
- Ennis Automotive No Mas Segundas Oportunidads!, 18 (Box 3)
- Ennis Automotive No Mas Segundas Oportunidads!, 19 (Box 3)
- No more second chances! Ennis Automotive, 20 (Box 3)
- Uniting at American Cabinet, 21 (Box 3)
  Video Portfolios Productions
- Uniting at American Cabinet, 22 (Box 3)
  Video Portfolio Productions
- Vote UNITE!, 23 (Box 3)
  New York Joint Board
- Vote UNITE!, 24 (Box 3)
- Vote UNITE!, 25 (Box 3)
- It's time we had a say, 26 (Box 3)
- It's time we had a say, 27 (Box 3)
- It's time we had a say, 28 (Box 3)
- UNITE! For a better future, 29 (Box 3)
- UNITE! For a better future, 30 (Box 3)
- Our chance for respect, 31 (Box 3)
- Our chance for respect, 32 (Box 3)
- Our chance for respect, 33 (Box 3)
- UNITE! For a better future, 34 (Box 3)
- Uniting at Crowe Rope, 35 (Box 3)
- Uniting at Crow Rope, 36 (Box 3)
- Uniting at Crow Rope, 37 (Box 3)
- Crowe Rope - No second chances, 38 (Box 3)
- It's time to take back our union / Es Hora de Retonar Nuestra Union, 39 (Box 3)
  English/Spanish
- It's time to take back our union / Es Hora de Retonar Nuestra Union, 40 (Box 3)
- It's time to take back our union / Es Hora de Retonar Nuestra Union, 41 (Box 3)
- Ahora es el momento para una Union Verdadera! - Ahora es el momento para UNnite!, 42 (Box 3)
- Ahora es el momento para una Union Verdadera! - Ahora es el momento para Unite!, 43 (Box 3)
- Ahora es el momento para una Union Verdadera! - Ahora es el momento para Unite!, 44 (Box 3)
- Unite - Tucker, Arlington, TX, 1997; 1 (Box 4)
  Spanish -- 3/30/1997
- Our Union is here to stay, 2 (Box 4)
- Our Union is here to stay, 3 (Box 4)
- Our Union is here to stay, 4 (Box 4)
- Tucker Housewares Union SI!, 5 (Box 4)
- Tucker Housewares Union YES!, 6 (Box 4)
- Tucker Housewares Union SI!, 7 (Box 4)
- UNITE Justice, 8 (Box 4)
- Si se Puede (Yes we can), 9 (Box 4)
  Spanish
- Si se Puede (Yes we can), 10 (Box 4)
  English
- UNITE Justice, 11 (Box 4)
- Wilen Vote, 12 (Box 4)
- Schottenstein - Value City -- August 1996, 13 (Box 4)
- Schottenstein - Value City -- August 1996, 14 (Box 4)
- Value City, 15 (Box 4)
  4 days later version
- Value City, 16 (Box 4)
  Blitz version
- Value City, 17 (Box 4)
- UNITE Cannon victory, 18 (Box 4)
- UNITE Cannon victory, 19 (Box 4)
- Innoculation -- Best Quotes: Unite testimonial -- w/title info slates 7/1996, 20 (Box 4)
- Innoculation -- Best quotes: Unite testimonial -- w/title info slates 7/1996, 21 (Box 4)
- Unite, 1997; 22 (Box 4)
  Tucker, Arlington, TX -- 3/30/1997 -- English
- Life into their days, 23 (Box 4)
  Nairobi Hospice Charitable Trust
- Fruit of the Loom (Companion video), 24 (Box 4)
- Goya - Wharehouse & Drivers UNITE, 25 (Box 4)
- Goya Wharehouse & Drivers UNITE, 26 (Box 4)
- Group Discussion 11/2 Eversharpe, 27 (Box 4)
  French and English
- AMITY Workers - UNITE for respect, 28 (Box 4)
- AMITY Workers - UNITE for respect, 29 (Box 4)
- AMITY Workers - UNITE for respect, 30 (Box 4)
- Tape 4 - Montreal, 31 (Box 4)
- Union Yes! (Hope Webbing), 32 (Box 4)
- Union SI! (Hope Webbing), 33 (Box 4)
- ACTWU Our past, our future, 34 (Box 4)
- Unidos y Orgullosos: A message for Fruit of the Loom workers -- ACTWU for Justice in the Valley, 35 (Box 4)
- Atlanta interviews -- 4/24/1998, 36 (Box 4)
  tape #1
- Atlanta interviews 4/24/1998, 37 (Box 4)
  tape #2
- Atlanta interviews -- 4/24/1998, 38 (Box 4)
  tape #3
- Montreal - Kristin Riggs, 39 (Box 4)
- 60 Minutes - Prison Industries, 1996; 40 (Box 4)
  10/20/1996
- Unlabeled, 41 (Box 4)
- UNITE! - Because every vote counts, 42 (Box 4)
- UNITE! - Because every vote counts, 43 (Box 4)
- UNITE! - Because every vote counts, 44 (Box 4)
- Roadmaster Video -- Si Si Puede, 1 (Box 5)
- Roadmaster Video -- Si Si Puede, 2 (Box 5)
- Roadmaster Video -- Si Si Puede, 3 (Box 5)
- Uniting at Roadmaster, 4 (Box 5)
- Uniting at Roadmaster, 5 (Box 5)
- Morse Petit Jean Campaign/A message from Jesse Jackson, 6 (Box 5)
- Jackson Speech - Louisville, GA 1/14/1990, 7 (Box 5)
- A message from Jesse Jackson, 8 (Box 5)
- Richmark Video - with news clips rally, 9 (Box 5)
- Richmark video with news clip rally, 10 (Box 5)
- Unite - Petit Jean, 11 (Box 5)
- Unite - Petit Jean, 12 (Box 5)
- Unite - Petit Jean, 13 (Box 5)
- No stopping us now -- Petit Jean Video, 14 (Box 5)
- Petit Jean Video - No stopping us now, 15 (Box 5)
- Kmart, 16 (Box 5)
- Richmark Video, 17 (Box 5)
- Wilen Victory Party, 18 (Box 5)
- We're protecting what's ours at K Mart UNITE!, 19 (Box 5)
- It's time we had a say, 20 (Box 5)
- UNITE - Petit Jean, 21 (Box 5)
- Leland Homan -- Tucker Housewares -- Arlington, Texas, 22 (Box 5)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 23 (Box 5)
- Sweating for a t-shirt, 24 (Box 5)
  by Global Exchange
- Unidos y orgullosos: a message for Fruit of the Loom Workers, 25 (Box 5)
  ACTWU - for Justice in the Valley
- Unidos y orgullosos: a message for Fruit of the Loom Workers, 26 (Box 5)
  ACTWU for Justice in the Valley
- Stop Sweatshops! The video, 27 (Box 5)
- Going Global, 28 (Box 5)
- Going Global, 29 (Box 5)
- Going Global, 30 (Box 5)
- Union Yes - 1989 - UYVC-004, 31 (Box 5)
- Vote YES!, 32 (Box 5)
- Union Yes - It's Union time at Perdue: Vote Yes - April 4, 33 (Box 5)
- Roadmaster, 1996; 34 (Box 5)
  Original video - Alabama - 1996
- Uniting at Roadmaster, 35 (Box 5)
- Uniting at Roadmaster, 36 (Box 5)
- Uniting at Roadmaster, 37 (Box 5)
- UNITE!: Stop Sweatshops Campaign -- December 1996, 38 (Box 5)
- Welcome to Roadmaster UNITE!, 39 (Box 5)
- Welcome to Roadmaster, 40 (Box 5)
- Welcome to Roadmaster, 41 (Box 5)
- Controll Track - Roadmaster #2, 42 (Box 5)
- Arriba -- Nuevo Mexico -- Let's go Union, 43 (Box 5)
- Arriba Nuevo Mexico -- Ariba la Union, 44 (Box 5)
- Unite - Show #2 - July 17, 1997, 1 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #1 - July 15, 1997, 2 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #3 - July 20, 1997, 3 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #11 - August 3, 1997, 4 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #11 - August 3, 1997, 5 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #4 - July 21, 1997, 6 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #4 - July 21, 1997, 7 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #3 - July 20, 1997, 8 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #3 - July 20, 1997, 9 (Box 6)
- UNITE - wed. 8/6/ video, 10 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #12 - August 4, 1997, 11 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #12 - August 4, 1997, 12 (Box 6)
- Unite - Show #12 - August 4, 1997, 13 (Box 6)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 14 (Box 6)
  Political Action Video - UNITE
- What happened to the American Dream?, 15 (Box 6)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 16 (Box 6)
- Lear Union Workers do better, 1997; 17 (Box 6)
  July 19, 1997
- Lear Union Workers do better, 1997; 18 (Box 6)
  July 20, 1997
- Unite - Show #17 - August 12, 1997, 19 (Box 6)
- Misc.: (OT, Treatment, Ins., Negot., Union/Co. Cooperation, A.P.), 1996; 20 (Box 6)
  Best quotes: Unite testimonial w/title info slates 7/1996
- Endorsement (Solidarity), 1996; 21 (Box 6)
- Convention of UNITE, AFL-CIO,CLC; Miami Beach, FL -- 6/29-30/1995, 22 (Box 6)
- Window burn - LTC -- Ohio Central Slater Conference - Cleveland; V.O. and Union Testimonials (Some Spanish), 23 (Box 6)
  tape 2/2
- Central States Conf. - Cleveland, 24 (Box 6)
  Master for Edit - tape 1/2
- Ohio and Central States Conference - Cleveland; V.O. and Union testimonials (Some Spanish), 1995; 25 (Box 6)
  tape 2/2 -- 10/21/1995
- UNITE - How to defend your rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 26 (Box 6)
- UNITE - How to defend your rights: Immigrant Garment Workers Unite, 27 (Box 6)
  Chinese version
- Voice, Rights, Respect, 1996; 28 (Box 6)
  Best quotes: Unite testimonial 2/title info slates 7/1996
- Success and Unions - Good for business, 1996; 29 (Box 6)
- Convention of UNITE, AFL-CIO,CLC - Miami Beach, FL -- 6/29-30/1995, 30 (Box 6)
- Convention of UNITE, AFL-CIO,CLC - Miami Beach, FL -- 6/29-30/1995, 31 (Box 6)
- Contract wins/gains (incl. wages), 1996; 32 (Box 6)
  Best quotes: UNITE testimonial w/title info slates 7/1996
- UNITE Show #13 -- August 5, 1997, 33 (Box 6)
  tape one
- Convention interviews (1995), 34 (Box 6)
- 1995 UNITE Convention Highlights, 35 (Box 6)
- SEIU Nursing Home Division "A Time for a change" -- 3/16/2000, 36 (Box 6)
- Miami #4 -6/12/1996 -- Little Havana and Robert Pierson, 37 (Box 6)
- Miami Nurse Home Press Conf. #1 and #2, 38 (Box 6)
- Miami #8, 39 (Box 6)
- Miami tapes 6, 7, 40 (Box 6)
- Train Stories, 41 (Box 6)
- Train stories, 42 (Box 6)
- Miami shoot #3 - Nursing Homes - Tampa, 43 (Box 6)
- Nursing Homes - Tampa, 44 (Box 6)
- Activities at CMA Cable Company Bolivar, Ohio, 1994; 1 (Box 7)
  Thursday October 27 and Friday October 28, 1994 -- Unedited Master Tape
- Findlay Industries #1, 2 (Box 7)
- Findlay Industries #1 -- Worker interviews, 3 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Tamil, 4 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Tamil, 5 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Laotian, 6 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Chinese, 7 (Box 7)
- Flex, CMA Worker interviews, 8 (Box 7)
- Flex, CMA Worker interviews, 9 (Box 7)
- Convention 1995 Merger Video, 10 (Box 7)
- Jonbil -- August 1995, 11 (Box 7)
- Jonbil August 1995, 12 (Box 7)
- Jonbil -- Short version, 13 (Box 7)
- Jonbil Workers -- Its Union time, 14 (Box 7)
- Make it happen -- Convention video, 15 (Box 7)
- Tape 1 Jonbil suits, 16 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless English, 17 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless English, 18 (Box 7)
- Activities at CMA Cable Co. -- bolivar, Ohio; October 27 and 28, 1994, 19 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless English, 20 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless English, 21 (Box 7)
- Peerless -- 1st draft -- English, 22 (Box 7)
- Breaking the silence -- The fight for justice at Peerless, 23 (Box 7)
- Peerless -- 1st draft -- English, 24 (Box 7)
- Peerless - San Antonio, Texas, 25 (Box 7)
- Breaking the silence -- The fight for justice at Peerless, 26 (Box 7)
- Breaking the silence -- The fight for Justice at Peerless, 27 (Box 7)
- Peerless Clothing/Macy's Rally, 28 (Box 7)
  New York Coverage - Schedule enclosed
- Des employes de la cie Peerless ont l'intention de poursuivre la compagnie, 29 (Box 7)
- Justice for Peerless Workers II, 30 (Box 7)
- Justice for Peerless Workers II, 31 (Box 7)
- Peerless/Macy's - Atlanta -- 6/1/1996, 32 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Vietnamese, 33 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless French, 34 (Box 7)
- Peerless Workers for Justice I, 35 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Creole, 36 (Box 7)
- Peerless Workers for Justice I, 37 (Box 7)
- UNITE! Tape -- June 1995, 38 (Box 7)
- UNITE! Convention 1995, 39 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Spanish, 40 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Bengali, 41 (Box 7)
- SVTI Peerless Tagalug, 42 (Box 7)
- UNITE Convention Program 1995, 43 (Box 7)
- Make It Happen: Convention Video, 44 (Box 7)
  Copy 2.
- UNITE It's our turn to Unite -- 4/8/2000, 1 (Box 8)
- Dick Reese Captive, 2 (Box 8)
- 25th Hour Dialogue -- 8/6 Fitz, 3 (Box 8)
- UNITE! Together we can do it better, 4 (Box 8)
- Adidas Protest - US Open/September 7, 1995, 5 (Box 8)
- Former Pro Union-Buster Marty Levitt Tells All, 6 (Box 8)
- UNITE - Es Hora de Tener una Union Verdadera, 7 (Box 8)
- It's time for a real Union! It's time for UNITE!, 8 (Box 8)
- UNITE Get ready to Unite, 9 (Box 8)
- December 21What time is it? Union time!, 10 (Box 8)
- Killer Needles: Our fight to stop a health care epidemic, 11 (Box 8)
- There's no stopping us now!, 12 (Box 8)
- It's up to you!, 13 (Box 8)
- Contract wins/gains (Incl. wages), 1996; 14 (Box 8)
- It's time for a Real Union! It's time for UNITE!, 15 (Box 8)
- It's time for a real UNION! It's time for UNITE!, 16 (Box 8)
- Making it happen!, 17 (Box 8)
- Con Bang Cho Cong Nhan Peerless, 18 (Box 8)
- Justice pour les Travailleurs et les Travailleuses de Peerless!, 19 (Box 8)
  I version Francais
- Japan they don't talk about, 20 (Box 8)
- UNITE, 1997; 21 (Box 8)
  4/25/1997
- D.I.A.L., 22 (Box 8)
- Ain't no stopping us now, 23 (Box 8)
- UNITE Good for business, 24 (Box 8)
- Actions '96, 1996; 25 (Box 8)
- Make it happen -- Convention video, 26 (Box 8)
- Chinatown manpower project workplace literacy program - Garment related bilingual TV Broadcast Lessons, 27 (Box 8)
  episode 9 to 15
- UNIAO SIM! With a message from Father Pio, 28 (Box 8)
- Unite for a real union, 29 (Box 8)
- UNITE -- Words -- Face -- 1/25/1996, 30 (Box 8)
- Curtains -- Designing Women - CBS, 31 (Box 8)
- USWA Humanity Fund for a penny, 32 (Box 8)
- Ties that bind: we do the work, 33 (Box 8)
- Speech Reel #2, 34 (Box 8)
- Speech Reel #2, 35 (Box 8)
- Speech Real #1, 36 (Box 8)
- The Mobile Public Employees Union - UNITE -- Alan Hanson, 37 (Box 8)
- Hollaner - Chicago, 38 (Box 8)
- UNITE for a better UCP, 39 (Box 8)
- It's Union Time at Perdue! Vote Yes - April 4, 40 (Box 8)
- Injury by design Repetitive Strain Injuries, 41 (Box 8)
- National Linen, 42 (Box 8)
- National Linen - 1/1999, 43 (Box 8)
- Speech Reel #1, 44 (Box 8)
- Capitol Plastics - Honda Supplier, 1993; 1 (Box 9)
  Recognition Ceremony -- Oct. 8, 1993
- Margie's Story; A Community Approach, 2 (Box 9)
  2 excerpts from The Second Epidemic -- NYC Commission on Human Rights
- UNITE! Up-to-date violations: a shameful history, 3 (Box 9)
- Fairness at Fuqua, 4 (Box 9)
- Opportunity Knocking, 5 (Box 9)
- Fairness at Fuqua, 6 (Box 9)
- What could our future look like if the union got in?, 7 (Box 9)
- PowerIt's not just for bosses anymore! / Poder Ya no Solo Es Para Los Patrones!, 8 (Box 9)
- 7/28 -- John Nevin Message, 9 (Box 9)
- In the shadow of the tower, 10 (Box 9)
- Fury in the slaughterhouse - Every generation got it's own disease - When I'm dead and gone - Radio Orchid, 11 (Box 9)
  The RCA Records Label
- 7/28 - John Nevin Message, 12 (Box 9)
- UNITE - 2003 Convention Highlights, 13 (Box 9)
- Elka & Union Guy Part II // Teatu Call in 8/12, 14 (Box 9)
- UNITE Convention - Organizing/Final, 15 (Box 9)
- Thunderbolt and Lightfoot -- Brazil, 16 (Box 9)
  Mask
- IDMD - Tamil version, 17 (Box 9)
- IDMD - English version, 18 (Box 9)
- UNITE! A message from President Bruce Raynor, 19 (Box 9)
- UNITE, 20 (Box 9)
  Canada video
- UNITE for a better future -- 12/16/1997, 21 (Box 9)
- UNITE 2003 UNITE! Convention, 22 (Box 9)
- UNITE! Members Love New York, 23 (Box 9)
- Adelante con UNITE!, 24 (Box 9)
- Marshalls and Unite: a Winning Combination, 25 (Box 9)
- Marshalls and Unite: A Winning Combination, 26 (Box 9)
- UNITE! Campaign for the future, 2003; 27 (Box 9)
  May 2003 -- French language version
- Marshalls' -- Atlanta Distribution Center - A Union Success, 28 (Box 9)
- Fairness at Fuqua, 29 (Box 9)
- Marshalls' Atlanta Distribution Center -- A Union Success, 30 (Box 9)
- Marshalls' Atlanta Distribution Center -- A Union Success, 31 (Box 9)
- Were voting now!, 32 (Box 9)
  Master -- Pillowtex UNITE
- The Truth about Kenco, 33 (Box 9)
- UNITE - Campaign for the Future, 34 (Box 9)
- Fechheimer: the Truth behind the label, 35 (Box 9)
- UNITE Campaign for the future, 36 (Box 9)
- Unlabeled, 37 (Box 9)
  label is in a foreign language, (characters)
- Adelante con UNITE!, 38 (Box 9)
- Adelante con UNITE!, 39 (Box 9)
- Unlabeled, 40 (Box 9)
  Label in foreign language (characters) - Laotian version
- UNITE For a better future -- 12/16/1997, 41 (Box 9)
  Jeff Meltzer Editorial, Inc., Picture and Sound
- UNITE Southern Regional Video 1998, 42 (Box 9)
- Make it happen, 43 (Box 9)
- The Truth about Kenco, 44 (Box 9)
- UNITE Southern Regional Video 1998, 45 (Box 9)
- We won't back down, 1996; 46 (Box 9)
  Southern Regional Video 1996
- We won't back down, 1996; 47 (Box 9)
- Make it happen, 48 (Box 9)
- UNITE Southern Regional Video 1998, 49 (Box 9)
- Feccheimer - Meeting with Boss, 1998; 1 (Box 10)
  Close-ups - tape 2 - 10/1/1998
- Feccheimer - Meeting with Boss, 1998; 2 (Box 10)
  Wide shots - tape 1 - 10/1/1998
- Firestone Workers Unite for Change!, 3 (Box 10)
- Firestone Workers Unite for change!, 4 (Box 10)
- Partners in Prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 5 (Box 10)
- The Truth about Kenco, 6 (Box 10)
- Partners in Prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 7 (Box 10)
- Partners in Prevention: UNITE Safety and Health Committees in Action, 8 (Box 10)
- Crowe Rope No Second Chances - 12/16/1997, 9 (Box 10)
  Jeff Meltzer Editorial, Inc. Picture and Sound
- Crowe Rope No Second Chances -- 12/16/1997, 10 (Box 10)
- The Greenfield Research Workers Story: Why "Union Yes", 11 (Box 10)
- Uniting at Crowe Rope, 12 (Box 10)
- Marshalls and Unite: A winning combination, 13 (Box 10)
- Columbia Teach-In, October 3-4, 1996, 14 (Box 10)
- Columbia Teach-In, October 3-4, 1996, 15 (Box 10)
- Se merecen una voz, 16 (Box 10)
- Se merecen una voz, 17 (Box 10)
- American Cabinets - Conway to Kansas, 18 (Box 10)
- Uniting at American Cabinet, 19 (Box 10)
- The Greenfield Research Workers Story: Why "Union Yes", 20 (Box 10)
- Uniting at Crowe Rope, 21 (Box 10)
- El Tiempo es ya Kastrin UNITE, 22 (Box 10)
- Depende de Usted!, 23 (Box 10)
- Depende de Usted!, 24 (Box 10)
- American Cabinet - Victory Footage -- 7/10/1996, 25 (Box 10)
- American Cabinet -- Victory Footage -- 7/10/1996, 26 (Box 10)
- American Cabinet -- Victory Footage -- 7/10/1996, 27 (Box 10)
- CINTAS - Chicago, 28 (Box 10)
- CINTAS - Chicago, 29 (Box 10)
- CINTAS - Chicago, 30 (Box 10)
- Organizing Committee - Tues. June 29 - UNITE Convention 1999, 31 (Box 10)
- Organizing Committee - Tues. June 29 - UNITE Convention 1999, 32 (Box 10)